<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home of Eve Kolb on thelooter</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home of Eve Kolb on thelooter</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building Go Applications with Gitlab CI</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/blog/building_go_applications_with_gitlab_ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/blog/building_go_applications_with_gitlab_ci/</guid>
      <description>Intro Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve started building and deplyoing Go Applications with Gitlab CI. Today I wanna share how I build a Pipeline that aims to make your code more resilient and safe.&#xA;The Pipeline Steps of a Pipeline First we should identify the steps we need in a Pipeline. We&amp;rsquo;ll split those into steps that verify and steps that transform, and steps that publish.&#xA;Verify Linting Unit Tests / Integration Tests SAST Secret Detection Dependency Scanning Transform Building Verification Linter The first Step we&amp;rsquo;re gonna add is the Linter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my little corner of the internet.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m Eve and I love building things and learning new stuff. I&amp;rsquo;m from Germany and currently work as a Junior Dev/Devops Engineer.&#xA;I love teaching new things to people, so stick around to learn. I also love building communities around compassion and understanding.&#xA;If you have any questions about Minecraft Development, Observability, don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to ask me. Even better if you also send Cat photos (I love cats).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D2Checkpoint</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/projects/d2checkpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/projects/d2checkpoint/</guid>
      <description>D2Checkpoint.com is a website that hosts checkpoints for raids and dungeons in the game Destiny 2. We provide a convenient way for players to pick up popular checkpoints, so they can focus on completing content.&#xA;The project has continued to attract a lot of traffic with over 1.000.000 unique users and around 100.000 monthly users. Its build using Go, Kubernetes and Svelte&#xA;Website: https://d2checkpoint.com Community: https://discord.gg/d2checkpoint </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EventChecker</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/projects/eventchecker/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/projects/eventchecker/</guid>
      <description>EventChecker is a Paper Plugin that allows developers to check for Events their Paper Server sends. It also includes filtering functionality.&#xA;Written in Kotlin and build with Gradle&#xA;Github: https://github.com/thelooter/EventChecker </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lab&#43; for Gitlab</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/projects/labplus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/projects/labplus/</guid>
      <description> NOTE&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m not the original author of this App. I forked it when the repository seemed abandoned&#xA;Lab+ lets you see the latest happenings wherever you are, reply to issues so they can be taken care of faster, manage and organise projects with labels, browse your files, code and more!&#xA;currently thinking about rewriting it in Kotlin with Compose Multiplatform&#xA;Github: https://github.com/thelooter/labplus_for_gitlab </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mockbukkit</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/projects/mockbukkit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/projects/mockbukkit/</guid>
      <description>MockBukkit is a framework that makes the unit testing of Bukkit plugins a whole lot easier. It aims to be provide complete mock implementation of CraftBukkit that can be completely controlled from a unit test.&#xA;Written with Java, JUnit, Hamcrest and Gradle&#xA;Github: https://github.com/MockBukkit/Mockbukkit Community: https://discord.gg/3Wz7CrWHSz Maven: https://mvnrepository.com/artifact/com.github.seeseemelk/MockBukkit-v1.20 </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
